ICE IS THERE BECAUSE OF THE DERELICTION OF DUTY BY BIDEN AND THE DEMOCRATS.
YOU HAVE BLACK WOMEN WITH MAGA HATS ON IN CHICAGO, ALL OVER THE PLACE.
THEY WANT THE GUARD TO COME IN.
THERE WAS ONE WOMAN, SHE WAS GREAT TODAY, SHE SAID, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I DON'T CARE IF IT'S THE NATIONAL GUARD, THE ARMY, THE MARINES, THE AIR FORCE.
I DON'T CARE WHO COMES IN AS LONG AS WE'RE SAFE.
AND THAT'S THE WAY MOST OF THE PUBLIC FEELS.
WHY DON'T DEMOCRATS WANT TO PROTECT BLACK WOMEN?
FIRST, THEY DIDN'T STAND UP FOR BLACK KIDS WITH CANCER.
NOW THIS, Jussie Smollett GOT THE BENEFIT OF THE DOUBT IN CHICAGO, BUT NOT ICE.
DEMOCRATS KEEP SAYING THIS IS A CIVIL WAR.
WELL, TRUMP'S THE ONE TRYING TO LIBERATE BLACK AMERICANS WHILE THEY'RE DEMANDING TO KNOW WHO'S
GOING TO PICK THEIR CROPS.